(忆往昔)
-你好  兄弟  -凯文
- Hello, brother. - Kelvin.
-你还记得  -你在这儿做什么
- Oh, you remember? - What are you doing here?
跟你的目的一样
Same reason as you.
我们互帮互助一下如何
So what do you say we help each other out?
你帮我们找到凯莉·克莱恩
You help us track down Kelly Kline,
天堂就欢迎你回去
and you will be welcomed back into the fold.
你有权那么做
And you have the power to do that?
没有  我只是传个信儿
Oh, no. I can't. I'm just the messenger.
但约书亚有权
But Joshua can.
我们只求你听听我们说
All we ask is that you hear us,
拜托  小卡  我给你打过三通电话了
Come on, Cass. I've called you three times now.
你说你是个恶魔
And you said you were a demon.
我是个恶魔  你是罗斯玛丽  怀着孩子
I'm a demon, you're Rosemary, complete with baby.
凯莉  天使  温家兄弟  那些好人
Kelly, the angels? The Winchesters? The good guys?
他们都想要你死
They want you dead.
但我可以保护你  我可以保护你儿子
But I can protect you. I can protect your son.
小卡  是我
Cass, it's me.
我尝试联系你好几天了
I've been trying to get ahold of you for days.
冷静点  跟我走
Stay cool. Walk with me.
-我们想帮忙  -你管这叫帮忙
- We wanna help. - You call this helping?
她来了
She's here.
有小卡的消息了吗
you hear anything from Cass yet?
没有  还失踪着
No. Still MIA.
-你觉得他还好吧  -我不知道
- You think he's all right? - I don't know.
看来  米克让萨姆和迪恩
Apparently, Mick let Sam and Dean
拿走了柯尔特枪
get their hands on the bloody Colt.
欢迎回来  亲爱的
Welcome back, sweetheart.
(如今)
该服用维他命了
Vitamin time.
别闹
Don't.
不要
No.
乖乖的
Be a good girl.
好了
There.
不是吧  小凯
Really, Kel?
不吃药
Not taking your pills,
挑食
picking at your food...
不洗澡
refusing to bathe?
不要再这样不尊重你体内的神了
Stop disrespecting the God inside of you.
他会害死我的
He's gonna kill me.
是啊
Yeah.
而且他不会停手于此
And he's not gonna stop there.
每一个可悲软弱的人类
Every sad, weak human,
每一个刻板的天使
every tight-ass angel,
每一个可怜巴巴的恶魔
every sniveling demon...
都会被吞噬
they'll all be consumed.
随你吧
So go ahead.
玩你的游戏吧
Play your games.
但不管你是健康还是病怏怏  肮脏还是干净
But whether you're healthy or sick, filthy or clean,
他都会降生
He will be born.
那将多愉快
Good times.
但在那之前
But until then...
算帮我们俩个忙
Do us both a favor?
洗个澡吧
Take a bath.
我爱你
I love you.
但我们不能在一起
But we won't ever be together.
我们两个都不会有幸福结局
There is no happy ending for either of us.
如果她的话是真的
And if what she said is true...
如果你真的是这样的
if this is what you really are...
你真会对世界做出那样的事
what you'll do to the world,
那么多痛苦
all that pain,
那么多死亡
all that death,
我不能允许那种事发生
I can't let that happen.
对不起
I'm sorry.
[邪恶力量 第12季第19集]
干什么呢  美丽心灵
What's up, Beautiful Mind?
我觉得我们追踪不到大衮
Guess I just figured we can't exactly track Dagon,
就去补习了一下拿非利人的知识
so I've been reading up on nephilim,
想看看还有多久
trying to figure out how much time we have before --
-小路西法出生  -嗯
- 'Lil Lucifer pops? - Yeah.
好吧  我们知道凯莉是
Okay, so we know Kelly got pregnant
12月初怀的孕
sometime in early December.
据传说  拿非利人不需要九月怀胎
According to the lore, nephilim don't need 9 months
就满妊娠期
to get to full term,
我觉得她大概会在
so I think she will be
5月8日左右产子
giving birth around May 18th.
-那么  -我们还有不到一个月来找她
- Which means... - We have less than a month to find her.
是啊  而且毫无头绪
Yeah, and exactly no idea where to start.
好吧  就算我们找到了她  又如何
Okay, but even if we do find her, what then?
我不知道
I don't know.
我...
I mean, I-I...
小卡
Cass.
你们好
Hello.
你没事
You're all right.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我替萨姆重说一遍
Let me rephrase that for Sam.
你小子跑哪去了
Where the hell have you been?
为什么不接我们的电话
And why have you ignored our phone calls?
我去的地方  信号
Where I was, the -- the reception
不好
was, uh...poor.
没信号吗
No bars?
没信号  这就是他的借口
No bars. That's his excuse.
我去了天堂  我去跟天使合作了
I was in Heaven. I was working with the angels.
当我看到大衮抓走了凯莉
When I saw Dagon had captured Kelly,
我觉得他们能帮上忙
I-I thought they could help.
怎么样呢
And?
没结果
Nothing.
至少你回来了
Well, at least you're back.
我们很高兴你回来了
We're glad you're back.
是吗
Really?
不  很抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
因为你在天堂毫无进展的时候
Okay, 'cause while you were striking out in Heaven,
我们可是有机会杀死大衮  但输了
we had a shot at Dagon, and we lost.
我知道
I know.
我收到你的留言了
I...received your messages.
是吗  你收到留言啦
Oh, you did -- you did receive the messages?
-好啊  那很好  -迪恩
- Okay, that's good. - Dean.
那么你不仅丢下了我们
So not only were you ditching us,
还无视我们
but you were also ignoring us?
太棒了
That's great.
因为我们当时真需要后援
'Cause we really could've used the backup.
但你忙着
But, uh, you were too busy with, um...
什么来着
What was it?
-没结果  -迪恩
- Nothing? - Dean, I --
你是怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with you, man?
无所谓了
You know, whatever. That's...
嗯  欢迎回来
Yeah. Welcome back.
迪恩
Dean, y--
对不起  迪恩
Sorry, Dean.
我就想还这个
I just wanted to return this.
(迪恩最爱13首)
这是礼物
It's a gift.
你要留着的
You keep those.
小卡  你不能
Cass, you can't...
现在事情这么多
With everything that's going on,
你不能这么突然消失
you can't just go dark like that.
我们都不知道你是怎么了
We didn't know what happened to you.
我们很担心  这样不好
We were worried. That's not okay.
我不是有意增添你的烦恼的
Well, I didn't mean to add to your distress.
我...
I...
迪恩  我总是失败
Dean, I just keep failing.
一次又一次
Again and again.
你被抓走时
When you were taken,
我找了几个月都找不到你
I searched for months and I couldn't find you.
然后凯莉从我眼皮下逃跑  我又找不到她
And then Kelly escaped on my watch, and I couldn't find her.
我就是想
And I just wanted...
我需要带着胜利回来找你
I needed to come back here with a win for you.
也是为我自己
For myself.
你以为只有你运气不佳吗
You think you're the only one rolling snake eyes here?
她本来在我和萨姆手里
Me and Sam, we had her.
但后来又把她弄丢了
We had Kelly and we lost her.
如果你们再找到她呢
And if you find her again?
萨姆在查呢
Sam's working on it.
当然  他一心想找到一个
Of course, he's hell-bent on finding something
不需要杀她和那孩子的办法
that doesn't mean killing her or her kid.
嗯  如果他找不到呢
Right. And if he doesn't find something?
如果你们没时间了
If you run out of time,
你们两个
could either of you
能杀一个无辜者吗
kill an innocent?
我们会找到更好的办法的
We will find a better way.
我们吗
You mean, we?
是的  傻蛋  我们
Yes, dumbass. We.
你  我  和萨姆
You, me, and Sam,
我们在一起时更好
we're just better together.
既然你回来了  自由意志队加油吧
So now that you're back, let's go, Team Free Will.
我们去做个了断
Let's get it done.
好啊
I'd like that.
很好
Great.
我想喝杯啤酒
And I'd like a beer.
你做了什么
What did you do?
他不许我死
He wouldn't let me die.
行了  哥们  睡会儿吧
Come on, man. Get some sleep, all right?
你今晚找不到大衮的
You're not gonna find Dagon tonight.
迪恩  如果我们一直以来思路
Dean, what if we've been going about this whole thing
都错了呢
the wrong way, you know?
我们追踪不到大衮  是吧
I-I mean, we -- we can't track Dagon, right?
我们知道  我们试过了
We know that. We've tried.
但如果我们能追踪那个拿非利人呢
But -- but what if we can track the nephilim?
怎么追踪
How?
这个嘛
Well...
好吧  那孩子是半天使  是吧
Okay, the baby's half-angel, right?
记得嘉德利尔吗
So remember Gadreel?
那个占用了你的身体的疯子天使吗
The psycho angel who took your body for a test drive?
-记得  他咋了  -好吧
- Yeah, what about him? - All right, well...
有个咒语
there was this, uh, there was this spell --
小卡和我当时为找他研究过
Cass and I were working on it -- to -- to find him.
是啊  但不好使
Yeah, but it didn't work.
-是啊  -你需要嘉德利尔的能量
- Yeah. - You needed Gadreel's grace,
而他抽不到足够的
and he couldn't yank enough out of you.
当然了
Of course.
当然什么
Of course what?
我是个白痴
Of course I am an idiot.
-这我不反对  -别闹  迪恩
- Well, there's no argument there. - No, stop. Dean...
能量抽取
The grace extraction.
追踪咒没成功  是吧
The tracking spell was a bust, right?
但抽取仪式成功了
But -- but the extraction ritual worked.
-那又怎样  -如果小卡对凯莉的孩子用呢
- So? - So what if Cass used it on Kelly's kid?
一个拿非利人就是有天使能量的
I mean, a-a nephilim's just a human soul
人类灵魂  是吧
with angelic grace, right?
那如果除去能量
So you remove the grace --
-孩子就是个孩子了  -孩子就是个孩子了
- Kid's just a kid. - Kid's just a kid.
这样  凯莉就不用死
That way, Kelly wouldn't have to die,
她的孩子也不用死了
and -- and neither would her baby.
-我去  -我去
- Hot damn. - Hot damn.
当然  我们还得先找到凯莉
I mean, we still obviously have to find Kelly in the first place.
-这也只是个理论  -不不
- I mean, it's just a theory, but -- - No, no, no. No, no.
这
That's...
这就是办法
This is it.
这就是办法  萨姆
This is it, Sam.
我去找小卡
I'll get Cass.
小卡
Cass?
Yo, Cass?
你真以为那会成功吗
You really thought that was gonna work?
你有机会成为圣母玛利亚2.0
You get the chance to be Mary of Nazareth, Part 2,
邪恶基督版的
Evil Jesus Edition.
-他不是  -什么
- He's not. - Excuse me?
他不是  我的宝宝不是邪恶的  他救了我
He's not. My baby's not evil. He saved me.
你以为是这么回事吗
That's what you think happened?
他是在自救
He saved himself.
他才不在乎你
He doesn't care about you.
什么都没变
Nothing's changed.
他会生  你会死
He's born, you die.
但别担心
But don't worry.
我会在的  陪在他身边
I'll be there, right by his side,
抚育他  爱他
to nurture him, love him,
帮他
to help him to...
杀死一切
kill everything.
知道吗
You know,
就像个妈妈那样
like a mother should.
你好  兄弟  拿到了吗
Hello, brother. Is it done?
是的
Yes.
子弹呢
Bullets?
枪膛里只有两发
There were only two in the chamber,
我又不能再多要
and I couldn't exactly ask for more.
足够了
It's enough.
-一发给大衮  -嗯
- One for Dagon... - Yeah.
一发给凯莉
One for Kelly.
-他们很接近  -我们感应到的天堂震动
- They're close. - The celestial pulse we felt,
约书亚追踪到了附近的一栋房子
Joshua tracked it to a house nearby.
(迪恩来电)
(未接来电  迪恩)
你做的是对的
You're doing the right thing, you know.
执行约书亚的计划
Committing to Joshua's plan,
把天使置于温家人之前
putting angelkind above the Winchesters.
你在天堂的名誉...
I mean, your reputation in Heaven is --
这跟我的名誉毫无关系
This has nothing to do with my reputation.
我这么做是为了温家兄弟
I am doing this for the Winchesters.
我偷走柯尔特枪
I-I stole the Colt
就是为了不让他们搅进来
to keep them out of this mission
让他们不用对付大衮
and to keep them safe from Dagon,
我...
and I...
我会杀了那姑娘
I will kill this girl
这样萨姆和迪恩就不用那么做了
so that Sam and Dean don't have to.
荷宰
Hozai.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
大衮  那姑娘
Dagon, the girl,
都在房子里
they're in the house.
好戏开场了
Showtime.
我们还有五秒
And now we've got 5 seconds
看到更多超级金句提示  并赢得大奖
to see more of the Super Catch Phrase and win the bank.
开始吧
Here we go.
辛迪  价值350美元  说出它是什么
Cindy, for $350, tell us what it is.
举重
Pumping iron?
不对
Not right.
奇普和辛迪
Chip and Cindy --
观众席上很多人认为他们知道
Got a lot of people in the audience who think they know,
你有接手机会
but we have a Toss Up Catch Phrase for you.
你的对手知道  但她不能答
Now your opponent knows, but she can't guess.
只有你能答  价值400美元
Only you are entitled. There's $400 in the bank.
-奇普  说答案  -铁幕
- Chip, what is it? - The Iron Curtain!
不
No!
太棒了
Yes!
我太激动了
I got so excited there myself...
说错了
that I went to the opposite thing.
真没想到
Well, whatcha know?
找到那姑娘
Find the girl.
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
这是我的语音信箱
This is my voicemail.
请留你的语音邮件
Make your voice...A mail.
我猜猜  没人接
Let me guess -- no answer.
小卡是怎么把柯尔特枪从保险箱里
I mean, how did Cass even get the Colt out of the safe
拿出来的
in the first place?
迪恩  你把柯尔特枪放回保险箱了吧
Dean, you -- you put the Colt back in the safe, right?
迪恩
Dean?
-就放在我枕头下面  -你
- It was under my pillow. - It...
我喜欢把它放身边
I like to keep it close.
他来我房间耍了我
He came into my room and he played me.
他把我们都耍了
Yeah, he played us both.
我们找到他  然后揍扁他
Well, I say we find him and we kick his feathered ass.
迪恩  小卡拿走柯尔特枪
Dean, Cass wouldn't have taken the Colt
肯定是想对付什么大家伙
if he wasn't going up against something big.
好吧  那我们找到他  搞清情况
Okay, I say we find him, figure out what's going on,
然后揍扁他
and then we kick his feathered ass.
看来你终于抓到我了
Guess you finally caught me.
刚刚在地下室
Back there in the basement...
你是来杀我的
you came to kill me.
但你没有
But you didn't.
谢谢你
Thank you.
别谢我
Please don't thank me.
我有任务要执行  但我失败了
I had a mission and I failed.
现在呢
And now?
我不知道
Now, I don't know.
我只是在尽量拉开
I'm just trying to put as much
你和大衮之间的距离
distance between you and Dagon as I can.
一切都好
Everything's fine.
刚安顿容器睡下了
Just put the container down for a nap.
是吗
Did you?
大衮
Dagon...
我知道你在撒谎
I know you're lying to me.
怎么回事
What happened?
吾王  我
My Lord, I...
告诉我
Tell me.
听着
Look, I...
天使  找到了我们
The angels, they found us.
其中一个抓走了她
One of them took her.
哪个
Which one?
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
等等  等等
Okay, wait a minute. Wait a minute.
你让温家兄弟的宠物狗
So you let the Winchesters' purse dog
抓走了我儿子
take my son?
我不...
I didn't...
我会找到他们的
I will find them.
当然  否则你的幻想
Yes, you will, or that little fantasy of yours,
统治天堂和人间
ruling Heaven and Earth,
你  我加宝宝三个
you, me, baby makes three...
那不是幻想  那是你对我的承诺
It's not a fantasy. That was your promise to me.
我再给你个承诺
Here's another promise for you --
找到我儿子
find my boy,
否则我将给你的折磨
or the torments I will visit upon you
会是无尽的
will be infinite.
我保证
Promise.
你去解决这事  大衮
You make this right, Dagon.
解决它
Make it right.
我会的
I will.
(北点汽车旅馆)
怎么回事
What's going on?
我在跟约书亚交流
I was communicating with Joshua.
他是个天使  我...
He's an angel. I, um...
我在接受指示
I was getting my orders.
我之前杀不了你
I couldn't kill you back there.
但现在  我要带你回天堂
But now, I will take you to Heaven.
你的生命将终结  你的宝宝也是
Your life will end, and your baby's, too.
那会迅速  没有痛苦
It'll be swift and painless.
不
No.
不  你不知道
No, you don't know...
如果不成功呢
What if it doesn't work?
没有人类能踏过那扇门还活下来
No human form can step through that gate and survive.
你们的灵魂将升入天堂
Your souls will ascend to Heaven,
你们的每个细胞
and every cell of your beings
都会回归宇宙
will return to the universe.
对不起  凯莉
I am sorry, Kelly.
那是路西法的儿子
The son of Lucifer...
他是人/大天使混血儿
this is a human/archangel hybrid.
他的力量
That power...
无法想象
it's beyond comprehension.
你的孩子
Your child
能让宇宙臣服
could bring the universe to its knees.
也或许能抬升它
Or lift it to its feet.
这个孩子  人之初性本善
This baby, nothing is born evil.
我不能冒险
I can't take that chance.
我们都不能
None of us can.
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Right.
自杀任务  没有应急方案
Suicide mission, no contingencies,
一堆废话
blah, blah, blah.
我相信你
I believe you.
你不知道卡西迪奥在哪
You don't know where Castiel is.
但他是个天使
But he's an angel,
你也是
you're an angel.
我觉得  如果你好好想
Got a feeling, ya dig deep enough,
能猜个八九不离十
you can make an excellent guess.
我凭什么告诉你
Why would I tell you?
你只是路西法绝望
You're just Lucifer's desperate,
粘人的跟班
clingy side piece.
因为做路西法的跟班
'Cause being Lucifer's side piece
也是有好处的
has its perks.
快想
Now think.
他去哪了
Where's he going?
WWCD
Wwcd.
卡西迪奥会怎么做
What would Castiel do?
你别让人看到
You need to keep out of sight
等我准备好继续上路
until I can get us back on the road.
我渴了  我就是想...
I'm thirsty. I just want...
坐下吧
Just...sit.
(怎么修车)
我出了一件事  卡西迪奥
Something happened to me, Castiel.
我丧失了希望  我企图...
I lost hope. I tried to...
自杀
I killed myself.
我割了腕
I slit my wrists.
我死了
I died.
然后
And then...
他救了我
He saved me.
他让我复活了
He brought me back to life.
这就是那阵震动
Well, that was the pulse.
我们在天堂感觉到了
We felt that in Heaven.
他的力量
His power...
他的灵魂涌过了我
his soul surged through me,
那感觉很棒
and it was good.
很纯  我觉得...
Pure. I feel...
我知道他是好的
I know he is good.
凯莉
Kelly...
你的孩子做的  那证明了他的力量
what your child did, that's a testament to his power,
但不能证明它的善良
but it's not proof of some goodness.
他需要你活着
He needs you alive.
或许吧
Maybe.
也或许是个奇迹
Or maybe it was a miracle.
或许我经历的一切
Maybe...maybe everything that I've been through,
我还需要经历的一切
everything that I still have to go through,
都是事出有因的
is happening for a reason.
或许这是一个计划的一部分
Maybe it's part of some plan.
不  不是的
No, it isn't.
我曾经相信过
I used to believe in
计划
a plan.
我曾经相信  我有使命
I used to believe that I had some mission.
但我如今已经经历了很多  终于知道
But I have been through enough now to know that
每个人都在临场发挥
everyone is just winging it.
有些人发挥得不好
Some of us quite badly.
路西法
Lucifer...
他只是在搞破坏
he's just breaking toys.
他在播种毁灭和混乱
He's sowing destruction and chaos,
这里面是没有什么大目标的
and there is no grand purpose at work.
你也没有什么特别角色
And there's no special role for you.
路西法占据鲁尼身体时
When Lucifer took over Rooney's body...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你刚好在那儿而已
You were just there.
我知道我的宝宝能为世界做好事
I know my baby can be good for this world.
凯莉  如果他降生
Kelly, if he's born...
你肯定会因此送命
that is not something you can survive.
就算你是对的
So even if you are right,
就算最坏的可能并非不可避免
and even if the worst isn't inevitable,
那你死后  又有谁能来照顾他
then who will care for him when you're gone?
谁呢
‭Who?
谁会足够强大能保护他
Who is strong enough to protect him
还能让他不受邪恶的影响
and to keep him from evil influences and
让他一直走正义之路
to keep him on the righteous path?
-怎么了  -他刚踢我了
- What? - ‭He just -- he just kicked.
你想...
Do you want to...
不了
No.
这没什么的  卡西迪奥
It's not a big deal, Castiel.
他每天要踢我20次呢
He does it, like, 20 times a day.
你别碰她
You stay away from her.
凯莉
Kelly?
那是我的
Yeah, that's mine.
你怎么想的
What the hell are you thinking, huh?
-迪恩  -干嘛
- Dean? - ‭What?!
迪恩
Dean!
凯莉
Kelly?
你怎么找到我们的
How did you find us?
你骗我的柯尔特枪时
Well, while you were scamming me for the Colt,
萨姆在你的手机里安了追踪应用
Sam put a tracking app on your phone.
小卡  你回来后  都不肯直视我们的眼睛
Cass, when you came back, you didn't even look us in the eye.
你想解释一下吗
You wanna explain what's going on here?
-嗯  我找到大衮了  -然后呢
- Yeah. I found Dagon. - ‭And?
-你杀掉她了吗  -没有  但是
- Did you kill her? - ‭No. But...
她很不好杀  好吗
She's difficult to kill, okay?
当然了
Yeah. ‭You think?
好吧  那你在这里做什么
All right, so what are you doing here, then?
我...
I...
-我的车坏了  -那
- My truck broke down. - ‭Then...
那你为什么不找我们  小卡  我们可以帮你的
Then why didn't you call us? Cass, we could've helped you.
我知道  我不希望你们搅进来
I know. I wanted to keep you out of this.
我是想保证你们的安全
I-I was trying to keep you safe.
你不是我们的保姆  小卡  那不是你的工作
You're not our babysitter, Cass, okay? That is not your job.
而且我们这辈子什么时候安全过了
And when in our whole lives have we ever been safe?
这是我的责任  因为这是我的计划
This is my responsibility because it is my plan.
你的计划
Your plan?
他要带我去天堂
He's taking me to Heaven.
你要带她去沙箱
You're taking her to the sandbox?
对  我要彻底终结这一切
Yes. I'm ending this, once and for all.
凯莉和她的宝宝必须死
Kelly and her baby have to die.
不  不需要  听着  我们找到别的办法了
No, they don't. Listen, we found another way.
你要是肯接电话就会知道了
And you would know that if you would answer your phone.
等等  你们说什么呢
Wait, what are you talking about?
你对我  对嘉德利尔做的事  记得吗
What you did with me, with -- with Gadreel, remember?
能量抽取
The -- the grace extraction.
我们拿走宝宝  拿非利人的能量
We take the grace from the baby, from the nephilim,
宝宝就变成
and then the baby just becomes --
-人类  -人类了
- Human. - ‭Human.
等等  那个抽取  险些要了你的命
Wait a minute. That extraction, it nearly killed you.
-是啊  但我没死  -因为我们没完成
- Yeah, but it didn't. - Because we didn't finish it.
我们都不知道这能否成功
We don't even know if this would work.
是有些问题  但至少是个计划
There are kinks, yes, but it's a plan.
总比必死无疑强
And it beats the hell out of certain death.
是吧
Am I right?
不
No.
凯莉  凯莉  等等的  听着
Hey, Kelly. Kelly. Hey, wait, wait. Wait a second, look.
我们无法想象你经历了什么
We -- we can't imagine what you've been through, okay?
但我们说过会想到别的办法  我们想到了
But we promised we'd find another way, and we did.
我们找到了别的办法  这能行的
We found a better way. This can work.
我要跟卡西迪奥去
I'm going with Castiel.
不  凯莉  你跟小卡走
No, Kelly, if you go with Cass,
就死定了  你宝宝也死定了
you die. Your baby dies.
我跟你走  你会夺走他的特别之处
I go with you, you take away the thing that makes him special.
如果你们都死了  那又有什么要紧
How does that matter if you're both dead?
那是唯一要紧的
That's the only thing that matters.
-这姑娘是疯了  -迪恩
- Okay, this girl has lost her mind. - ‭Hey, Dean.
现在  我们能不能去别处谈
Meanwhile, can we take this conversation elsewhere, guys?
我们在外面就是活靶子
We're kind of sitting ducks out here.
萨姆是对的  大衮在找凯莉  你的车坏了
Sam's right. Dagon is after Kelly. Your truck is broke down.
我们上宝贝车  回地堡
Why don't we get in the Impala, we'll head back to the bunker,
-然后谈谈  我们商量清楚  -嗯
- and we'll talk? We'll figure it out. - ‭Right.
好吧  我们谈谈
Okay, we'll talk.
-很好  -很好
- Great. - ‭Great.
-简直像赶猫一样困难  -是啊
- It's like herding cats. - Yeah.
怎么办  我们回地堡
Okay, so what? We -- we go back to the bunker
然后努力说服他们留下吗
and we just try to convince them to stay there forever?
迪恩  锁着呢
Dean. Locked.
不该是这样的
It's not supposed to happen this way.
凯莉
Kelly.
你干什么
What are you doing?
调头  你去哪
Turn around. Where are you going?
去天堂
To Heaven.
沙箱
The...sandbox,
只要你告诉我怎么去
if you tell me how to get there.
凯莉  我可以逼你停车的
Kelly, I can make you stop this car.
那你为什么不呢
Why haven't you?
好吧  你为什么这么做
Okay, why are you doing this?
因为他选了你  卡西迪奥
Because he chose you, Castiel.
你把手放在我肚子上时  我听到了他
When you put your hand on my stomach, I heard him.
他对我说话了
He spoke to me.
他说  虽然看上去很可怕
He told me that even if it seems scary,
只要我到达门口
if I just went to the gate,
只要我听从你的计划
if I just followed your plan,
你会确保他的降生
that you would make sure he was born.
萨姆和迪恩  他们想夺走他的力量
Sam and Dean, they want to take away his powers
那是因为他们害怕
because they're scared.
但我不怕
But I'm not.
-凯莉  -你问我等我死了
- Kelly, you -- ‭- You asked me who would protect him,
谁会保护他  引导他  我现在知道了
guide him when I'm gone. I know now.
是你
It's you.
我  那...
Me? That's...
我...
I...
我不是一个
I am not someone
你该寄于信心的人  凯莉
that you should put your faith in, Kelly.
我之前都杀不了大衮
I couldn't kill Dagon back there.
我失去了两个兄弟
I lost two of my men.
我背叛了我的朋友  家人
I betrayed my friends, my family.
这一切发生前
Before all this happened,
我是个二流政治宣传员
I was a cut-rate political flack
跟我的老板有着丢人的不专业的感情关系
in an embarrassingly unprofessional relationship with my boss.
我不知道为什么偏偏是我
I don't know why it's me.
也不知道为什么偏偏是你
And I don't know why it's you.
但我知道  这是我们注定的命运
But I know that we are destined for something here.
伟大的命运
Something great.
真希望我有你的信心
Well, I wish I had your faith.
你会有的
You will.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
哪部分  撒谎  天堂计划
What? The lying? The Heaven plan?
还是我修这辆破开车
Or the fact that I'm working on this stupid truck?
不  小卡是怎么了
No, I mean, what's wrong with Cass?
他这一年过得可不怎么样
Well, he hasn't exactly had a banner year.
想想看  路西法
I mean, think about it. Between Lucifer...
杀比莉  雷米尔
killing Billie, Ramiel,
他事事不顺
everything's been blowing up in his face.
他急着想要一次胜利
And he's so desperate for a win right now,
根本想不清楚了
he can't even see straight.
启动试试
Go ahead and give it a try.
-就是这里吗  -对
- This is it? - ‭This is it.
凯莉  你确定吗
Kelly, are you sure?
只要你在  我知道会没事的
As long as you're here, I know it's gonna be okay.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
凯莉
Kelly.
见到你们很高兴
It's good to see you.
你好  约书亚
Hello, Joshua.
我知道你肯定很害怕
I know you must be scared.
不必
But don't be.
你好  妹子
Hey, girl.
你俩就差一点啊
You two got so close!
如果我不是在最后关头及时赶到
If I hadn't made it here at the last possible second, uh...
开玩笑的
J.K.
我早就撬开了你哥们凯文的嘴
Flipped your pal Kelvin ages ago,
然后灭了他
then smoked him.
我在这儿等了好几个小时了
I've been here for hours.
你别碰她
You stay away from her.
怎么  不拿柯尔特枪吗
What, no Colt?
等等
Wait.
枪不在你手上了吗
You don't even have it anymore?
太好笑了
Hilarious.
看他啊  你的守护天使
Look at him, your angelic defender.
你真以为他能救你
You really thought he was gonna save you?
这个可悲  慌乱
This sad, fluttering,
毫无目标的小蛾子
aimless little moth?
不
No.
嗯
Yeah.
该把这个毁掉了
Time to take this off the board. ‭
不
No!
好了  谁想吃冰淇淋
Okay. Who wants ice cream?
小子  得了  这太可悲了
Kid, come on. It's just getting sad.
快跑
Run.
真可爱
Adorbs!
-小卡  -不
- Cass! - No!
怎么...
How...
称之为奇迹吧
Call it a miracle.
小卡
Cass?
那是怎么回事
What was that?
那是...
It was, um...
是我
It was me.
但也是
But it was also...
你受伤了
You're hurt.
谢谢你们来为我们而战
Thank you for coming to fight for us.
-你没事吧  -我没事
- Are you okay? - ‭I am.
我一直好迷茫
I've been so lost.
我现在不迷茫了
I'm not lost anymore.
我现在知道  这个孩子必须降生
And I know now that this child must be born
并且保留他的法力
with all of his power.
你不是真心的吧
You can't actually mean that.
我是真心的  我有了信心
Yes. I do. I have faith.
我们得走了
We have to go.
小卡  等等  等一下
Hey, Cass, wait a second. Wait, hold on. Just...
你们得信任我
You have to just trust me.
不不  等等  不管那玩意对你做了什么
No, no, no, wait. Okay, whatever that thing did to you,
我们不能就这么让你走掉
we're not just gonna let you walk away.
-是啊  那不可能的  -可能的
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen. - Yes, it is.
别
Don't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他跟你说了什么
What did he tell you?
他没说什么
He didn't tell me.
他给我看了
He showed me.
未来
The future.